second one street ball highly
第二个街球高
controversial moves like off the heey
第二个街球 高度争议性激烈的动作 就像脚踢下脚踢
充满争议的动作,像脚脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢下脚踢
controversial moves like off the heey
you know he throw it off the defender's
你知道他把它从辩护人那里扔掉了吗?
head it's only for when people are
人只为人头,人头只为人头
really low and they're really trying a
只有当人们非常低低的人 和他们真的在尝试
他们真的在尝试
really low and they're really trying a
lot I I get a ball between my legs a few
真的很低,他们真的很努力 我得到一个球 在我的两腿之间一些
我两腿之间有一球
lot I I get a ball between my legs a few
times here and go with my right hand
我得到了一个球 在我的两腿之间 几次在这里,走 与我的右手
此时此地,用我的右手
times here and go with my right hand
up rolling it down and then from there
在这里,然后用我的右手走 滚下来,然后从那里
然后从那里滚下来,然后从那里滚起来
up rolling it down and then from there
usually when do it people are like you
然后从那里滚下来 通常从那里开始 人们都像你一样
通常当做的时候 人们都像你一样
usually when do it people are like you
know what I'm saying surprise them so I
通常当做的时候 人们就像你知道我在说什么 给他们惊喜,所以我
知道我在说什么 给他们一个惊喜,所以我
know what I'm saying surprise them so I
try to go between their legs after so
知道我在给他们什么惊喜 所以我试着在他们两腿之间
之后试图在两腿之间走
try to go between their legs after so
it's like
试图在他们两腿之间走 之后,它就像
这就像
it's like
boom
碞钩 碞钩
繁荣
boom
to the bucket from there what do you
从那里到水桶,你是怎样的?
你们怎么从那里到水桶呢?
to the bucket from there what do you
think right hand so it's like it's this
从那里到桶 从那里,你认为什么 右手,所以它像这是
思考右手,所以它就像这个
think right hand so it's like it's this
oh you kind of go up this motion it's
右手思考右手,所以它就像它 就像这个哦,你种 上去这个动作,它
哦,你那种去 上这个动议 这是
oh you kind of go up this motion it's
quick before they can notice it up with
哦,你是那种去 上这个动议 它的快速之前,他们可以注意到它 与
在他们发觉前快一点
quick before they can notice it up with
your right it's quick there you go yeah
在他们用你的右右手注意到它之前,快快,快,快,快,快,你去那里耶
右右转,快,你走啊,是的
your right it's quick there you go yeah
boom boom tween and to the rack that's
右转,它快,在那里你去 耶,砰砰砰砰砰的Tweween和 架子,这是
蓬 蓬 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮 潮
boom boom tween and to the rack that's
that's what that's one like maybe you
繁荣潮的潮潮 和到架架 那就是那是什么 象你,也许你
那就是你这个样子
that's what that's one like maybe you
don't do with your friends right that's
这就是你对你的朋友 可能不会做那种事的原因
不要和你的朋友做,对吗?
don't do with your friends right that's
a tough one that's a tough one cuz I you
不要和你的朋友们做对了,这是个艰难的一个 艰难的一个,因为你
硬的,难的,因为你
a tough one that's a tough one cuz I you
don't want to hurt the other person
坚硬的 坚硬的 因为我不想伤害另一个人
不想伤害对方
don't want to hurt the other person
right
不想伤害对方
本字幕由AI大模型生成